

# Tran Le Phuong

# **Medical Communication Specialist**



# **Summary**

Being a Medical Communication Specialist in GSK with experiences of field management, event organization, support marketing, paper work and a lot skills such as selling skill, call detailing skill, management skill. 3-5 years of working as a content writer for a newspaper and a project in student life. Short-term goal is working as a good medical Rep in fields and support Product Manager and long-term goal is becoming a professional pharmaceutical marketer for next 5-10 years.



# **Experience**

07.2017 present

#### **Medical Communication Specialist**

**GlaxoSmithKline** 

- 1. Field Management Skill: Receive a new field, know how to approach and understand a field, HCPs, Problems quickly and also find out how to solve effectively.
- 2. Selling Skill: Determine key HCPs, right target, right potential, 80/20 in field that I can use time and efforts effectively to get the best results.
- 3. Call Detailing, Event Organizing: Ipad detailing, call detailing to HCPs, plan and set up a group detailing or web to group at a hospital.

#### 4. Results:

- Experienced fields: Chan Thuong Chinh Hinh, Thong Nhat, An Sinh, Tan Phu, Dai Phuoc Clinic and some private hospitals and poly clinics.
- Experienced Products: Antibiotic and Urology (Augmentin, Fortum, Zinnat, Avodart, Duodart).
- Growth 20-50% sale in fields especially private hospitals and polyclinics.

03.2017 -06.2017

#### **Content Writer (Part-time)**

HR.com.vn project (Career.vn company)

- Prepare and search content for the new launching website about Human Resources.
- Set up plans and Organize Events such as Workshops, Launching Event.
- Write new posts and also main content for a fan page.

12.2009 -

#### **Content Writer Collaborator**

09.2012

Thieu Nien Tien Phong Newspaper

- Writing news, short stories, long stories for the newspaper.
- Become "active writer" after 3 years of writing for this newspaper



Phone

0908071791

E-mail

Lorachan113@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lephuong-tran-6008565a/



**Selling and Negotiation skill** 



**Problem solving and Work and** management

Microsoft (power point, excel, word..)

**Event Organizing and** Presentation skill

**English Speaking, Writing and Translation** 



**English** 

lelts 6.5

Korean

Begining

**Translator Freelancer** 

2012 -2017

Happy skin

- Working as an English private tutor for 3 years in University.
- Translator for Happy skin- new website for beauty reviews.



# **Education**

10.2017 -02.2018

# Pharmaceutical Marketing program of BMG international School

- Understand and approach knowledge of a professional Marketer in Pharmaceuticals.
- Can work as a supporter for Product Manager.
- Graduation thesis " Makteting Plan for Prospan in 2018".

09.2012 -

07.2017

### **University of Medicine and Pharmacy**

- Certification of Bachelor: Good
- English: IELTS 6.5
- Certification in many contests and activities at University.